I used to work in private equity,
so I understand the banking system pretty well.
And the buy, borrow,
die method that a lot of people will use that are super rich
to basically put up their stocks as collateral and keep getting loan
so they live with the loan money
is essentially money printing, right?
Because they don't have to pay taxes on loans.
So Elon Musk can go say, hey,
loan me $2 billion and I'll put up my stock as collateral.
They give him $2 billion,
and now he doesn't have to pay taxes on that $2 billion.
He can throw it around willy nilly.
And the next question people will have is, hey,
what happens if he doesn't pay the bank back?
The government will bail the bank out.
Because if you owe the bank $2,000,
that's your problem. If you owe the bank two billion problems,
that's the bank's problem.
And you have to remember that when you have so much money
that you yourself are a market driving factor,
you have the leverage to create money at will.
Because if you're borrowing money from the bank
and all you need is collateral,
and your stock shares prices can be manipulated.
You can inflate your stock shares price,
take out a loan against it,
and surprise, you now have that super cheap loan.
And if the bank lends you a bunch of money,
guess who has to pay it back?
The government. Because if the bank doesn't,
they go Under it's truthfully a master class of having unlimited money